Harsh Kumar

Contact | Profile

254 Aspen wood drive Newmarket. ON

(437)-973-1246 Harshkumar021201@gmail.com

Key Skills

Persuasive Speaking Skills **Inventory Monitoring** Cash Register Operations Personable Demeanor **Guest Satisfaction Guest Orientation** Computer Skills **Exotic Service Request handling**

Certifications

EMERGENCY FIRST AID WITH CPR C & AED

Immediate Response Force Scarborough Sept 2022

Security Guard License

Immediate Response Force Dec 2022 - Dec 2024

Worker Health and Safety Awareness

Dec 2022

Knowledgeable Guest Service Representative experienced in busy hotel settings. Driven and dedicated with focus on delivering exemplary service. Skilled multi-tasker successful at meeting performance objectives and helping team members. Organized and dependable candidate successful at managing multiple priorities with a positive attitude. Willingness to take on added responsibilities to meet team goals.

Experience

Guest Service Representative

CCSAI Centennial College, Scarborough, ON

Sept 2022-Present

- Greeted visitors and customers upon arrival, offered assistance, and answered questions to build rapport and retention.
- Customer orientation and ability to adapt/respond to different types of characters
- Handle customer complaints by providing solutions, often within a time limit to ensure the customer is satisfied
- Learn the software systems used by the company to be able to communicate effectively with incoming inquiries
- Communicating and coordinating with colleagues as necessary
- Refer issues and questions to managers if necessary

Health and Wellness associate

Cube Packaging, Aurora, ON

Sept 2021 - Jan 2023

- Developing and implementing workplace health and wellness programs, including programs that promote healthy eating, physical activity.
- Conduct regular covid tests of employees making sure everyone is safe and healthier to maintain a safe working environment.
- Always make sure that employee is following health and wellness protocols
- Collaborating with other departments within the company to identify and address health and safety concerns, such as the use of hazardous materials or the risk of workplace injuries.
- Analyzing data and metrics related to employee health and wellness and using this information to continually improve workplace programs and policies.

Education

Software Engineering Technology-Artificial Intelligence
Centennial College, Toronto
Sept 2022 - Present

Technical Skills

- Strong knowledge of object-oriented programming concepts and principles
- Proficiency in object-oriented programming language such as Java, Python, or C# and front-end development tools like HTML, CSS
- Familiarity with design patterns and their applications in software development
- Experience with software development frameworks like Spring or Hibernate Knowledge of database systems and ability to write SQL queries
- Understanding of web technologies such as HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Ability to type accurately and quickly with a high level of accuracy